{
  "ent": [
    {
      "question": "Who is the most followed person on instagram?",
      "Answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option1": "Airana Grande",
      "option2": "Kylie Jenner",
      "option3": "Lionel Messi",
      "weight": 1,
      "id":"wqey"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian has won the oscar? ",
      "Answer": "Satyajit Ray",
      "option1": "Priyadarshan",
      "option2": "Yash Chopra",
      "option3": "Anurag Kashyap",
      "weight": 1,
      "id":"wqex"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the highest grossing movie in india?",
      "Answer": "Avengers:Endgame",
      "option1": "Avengers:Infinity War",
      "option2": "The Jungle Book",
      "option3": "FF8",
      "weight": 1,
      "id":"wqet"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian actor has shared sliver screen with tom cruise?",
      "Answer": "Anil Kapoor",
      "option1": "Akshay Kumar",
      "option2": "Anupam Kher",
      "option3": "Irrfan Khan",
      "weight": 1,
      "id":"wqea"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following movie was released in theaters?",
      "Answer": "Ramprasad ki tehrvi",
      "option1": "Gulabo Sitabo",
      "option2": "Laxmi bomb",
      "option3": "Ludo",
      "weight": 1,
      "id":"wqei"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the most followed person on instagram?",
      "Answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option1": "Airana Grande",
      "option2": "Kylie Jenner",
      "option3": "Lionel Messi",
      "weight": 1,
      "id":"wqry"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian has won the oscar? ",
      "Answer": "Satyajit Ray",
      "option1": "Priyadarshan",
      "option2": "Yash Chopra",
      "option3": "Anurag Kashyap",
      "weight": 1,
      "id":"waey"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the highest grossing movie in india?",
      "Answer": "Avengers:Endgame",
      "option1": "Avengers:Infinity War",
      "option2": "The Jungle Book",
      "option3": "FF8",
      "weight": 1,
      "id":"rqey"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian actor has shared sliver screen with tom cruise?",
      "Answer": "Anil Kapoor",
      "option1": "Akshay Kumar",
      "option2": "Anupam Kher",
      "option3": "Irrfan Khan",
      "weight": 1,
      "id":"whgy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following movie was released in theaters?",
      "Answer": "Ramprasad ki tehrvi",
      "option1": "Gulabo Sitabo",
      "option2": "Laxmi bomb",
      "option3": "Ludo",
      "weight": 1,
      "id":"ghfu"
    }
  ],
  
  "lit": [
    {
      "question": "atoz",
      "Answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option1": "Airana Grande",
      "option2": "Kylie Jenner",
      "option3": "Lionel Messi",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian has won the oscar? ",
      "Answer": "Satyajit Ray",
      "option1": "Priyadarshan",
      "option2": "Yash Chopra",
      "option3": "Anurag Kashyap",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the highest grossing movie in india?",
      "Answer": "Avengers:Endgame",
      "option1": "Avengers:Infinity War",
      "option2": "The Jungle Book",
      "option3": "FF8",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian actor has shared sliver screen with tom cruise?",
      "Answer": "Anil Kapoor",
      "option1": "Akshay Kumar",
      "option2": "Anupam Kher",
      "option3": "Irrfan Khan",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following movie was released in theaters?",
      "Answer": "Ramprasad ki tehrvi",
      "option1": "Gulabo Sitabo",
      "option2": "Laxmi bomb",
      "option3": "Ludo",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the most followed person on instagram?",
      "Answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option1": "Airana Grande",
      "option2": "Kylie Jenner",
      "option3": "Lionel Messi",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian has won the oscar? ",
      "Answer": "Satyajit Ray",
      "option1": "Priyadarshan",
      "option2": "Yash Chopra",
      "option3": "Anurag Kashyap",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the highest grossing movie in india?",
      "Answer": "Avengers:Endgame",
      "option1": "Avengers:Infinity War",
      "option2": "The Jungle Book",
      "option3": "FF8",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following indian actor has shared sliver screen with tom cruise?",
      "Answer": "Anil Kapoor",
      "option1": "Akshay Kumar",
      "option2": "Anupam Kher",
      "option3": "Irrfan Khan",
      "weight": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following movie was released in theaters?",
      "Answer": "Ramprasad ki tehrvi",
      "option1": "Gulabo Sitabo",
      "option2": "Laxmi bomb",
      "option3": "Ludo",
      "weight": 1
    }
  ],
  "subject_data": [
    {
      "username": "abcd",
      "subject_name": "lit",
      "highest_score": "23",
      "no_of_times_attempted": "3",
      "total_ques": 12,
      "max_marks": 12,
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "users": []
}